Jeremiah Wodke

Web Developer && Graphic Designer

(970) 391-2132 - jwodke@outlook.com

Experienced Web Developer with a demonstrated history of working with various technologies and platforms. Skilled in PHP, JavaScript, and modern frontend technologies. Experience building custom PHP applications, WordPress, WooCommerce, Shopify, BigCommerce and Web Project Management. My dream job consists of working with a small group of artisans who believe in beautiful code, ridiculous humor and that their software can help make our world a better place.

To view some of my personal projects please visit my portfolio website

http://jeremiahwodke.com

EXPERIENCE

MadWire Media, Fort Collins, CO — Custom Web Developer

May 1st, 2013 - Present

In my custom web developer position I create custom themes for Wordpress / WooCommerce, Shopify, and BigCommerce. I've also created custom PHP applications utilizing MVC and OOP paradigms.

Peak Studios, Remote/Boulder, CO — *Director of SEO*

Jan 1st, 2013 - July 15th 2016

I ran a small team whose tasks were to methodically analyze and increase the paid and organic SEO for numerous corporate franchises.

Corporations include; Chem-Dry and N-Hance Revolutionary Wood Renewal. Being that Peak Studios is a small consultancy I had to fill a lot of positions to meet the demands of our clients. I truly enjoyed working with our clients and watching our marketing strategy help their businesses grow.

Peak Studios, Remote/Boulder, CO — Web Developer

July 15th, 2015 - July 15th 2016

Assisting in the creation and/or maintainability of Wordpress templates for companies including but not limited to Chem-Dry, Marco's Pizza, Brand Journalists, N-Hance Wood Renewal and more.

Web Development

Wordpress, PHP, OOP, MVC,
MySQL, HTML5, CSS3,
JavaScript, jQuery,
Handlebars.js, Vue.js (green),
SASS, Bootstrap 3, Grunt,
NPM, Version Control (Git),
Liquid (Shopify), Jekyll, UX
Design Principles, REST Apis,
AJAX, CRUD, Cross-Browser
Testing, Responsive Web
Design

Graphic Design

High-Fidelity Mock-Ups, Photoshop, Asset Restoration, Asset Optimization, Professional Photograph, (Basic) Adobe Illustrator CS6

Internet Marketing

SEO Best Practices, Analytics, Keyword Research, Competitive Analysis, Site Auditing, Social Media Optimization, Powerlisting Software, Hootsuite, Website SEO, Video Optimization, PageRank Trust Flow Metrics, Citation Flow Metrics, A/B Testing and Optimization.

Chilson Recreational Facility, Loveland, CO — Facility Supervisor

Jan. 2011 - March. 2013

Responsibilities:

- Customer Support
- Overseeing Facility Attendants
- Facility Supervision for Night Events

Achievements at The Chilson Recreational Facility:

- Promoted to Facility Supervisor after 1 year of Employment

EDUCATION

Front Range Community College, Fort Collins, CO

2010 - 2012 (Some College)

→ Associates of Arts

Udacity, Online

2016

→ Frontend Developer Nanodegree

Flatiron School, Online

2016

- → JavaScript Basics
- → JavaScript Section of Full Stack Developer Program

Launch School, Online

2016

- → Programming Fundamentals
- → HTML and CSS

Udemy Online Learning

2016

- → Wordpress Theme Development with Bootstrap
- → The Complete Wordpress Developer Course
- → PHP for Beginners: Become a PHP Master
- → Photoshop for Web Design
- → Object Oriented Programming in PHP

REFERENCES

James Vucinovich

President / Client

Rossi Vucinovich PC Law Firm

(425) 646-8003 | jvucinovich@rvflegal.com

Quince Wyss

CEO Peak Studios

(303) 819-3968 | quince@peakstudios.com

Sam Ringleman

Web Developer at MadWire

(970) 460-4255 | sam@impactstud.io